SATO RINTARO

Master's student in Computer Science, Computer Vision

Email o 310rnomeado@gmail.com GitHub o https://github.com/rintarooo LinkedIn o https://www.linkedin.com/in/rintarooo

EDUCATION

Tsukuba University

Apr 2021 - present

Master's Program in Computer Science. Overall GPA: -

Kyushu UniversityUndergraduate Program in Mechanical Engineering.

Apr 2016 - Mar 2021

Overall GPA: 3.31/4.00

TECHNICAL STRENGTHS

LanguagesC, C++, Python, Java, C#TechnologiesMVC, HTML5, CSS, LatexToolsMikTex, Kile, NetbeansDatabasesMySql, Oracle, Sqlite, NoSqlCloud TechnologiesFirebase, AWS, Google Cloud

Version Control Github

WORK EXPERIENCE

Reversible Alphabet Pvt. Ltd., India

Jun 2017 - Dec 2018

Data Scientist

- · Created classification models for e-commerce websites using neural networks.
- · Achieved exposure towards classification optimalization techniques for further specialization.
- · Worked under an experenced Data Scientist and got deep insights related to optimization algorithms.

Irreversible Alphabet Pvt. Ltd., India

Jun 2016 - Dec 2016

Data Scientist

- · Created classification models for e-commerce websites using neural networks.
- · Achieved exposure towards classification optimalization techniques for further specialization.
- · Worked under an experenced Data Scientist and got deep insights related to optimization algorithms.

ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENTS

Project 'XYZ' won Best Project under Environmental Solver category under AICTE, Government of India

Recieved Scholarship For Higher Education(She) Component Under Inspire Scheme worth INR 4,00,000

Achived A Grade in Diploma in Computer Science from IBM

Won First Prize in Zonal technical quiz Competition Organized by IIT, Mumbai.

Project 'XYZ' won Best Project under Environmental Solver category under AICTE, Government of India

Recieved Scholarship For Higher Education(She) Component Under Inspire Scheme worth INR 4,00,000

Achived A Grade in Diploma in Computer Science from IBM

Won First Prize in Zonal technical quiz Competition Organized by IIT, Mumbai.

EXTRA-CIRRUCULAR

Attended a workshop on Machine Learning and artificial intelligence from faculties of IIT Roorkee in 2019 and won zonal round for the challenge presented.

Member of the Institute of Engineers since 2017.

Completed Basic Leadership Training under Project NSS, Gujarat

Attended a workshop on Machine Learning and artificial intelligence from faculties of IIT Roorkee in 2019 and won zonal round for the challenge presented.

Member of the Institute of Engineers since 2017.

Completed Basic Leadership Training under Project NSS, Gujarat

Attended a workshop on Machine Learning and artificial intelligence from faculties of IIT Roorkee in 2019 and won zonal round for the challenge presented.

Member of the Institute of Engineers since 2017.

Completed Basic Leadership Training under Project NSS, Gujarat

RESEARCH PROFILE

Student President, Technology and Research, IIT Gandhinagar

Publication: ABC, IOT IEEE Transactions (Impact Factor: 9.3, Status: Published)

Student President, Technology and Research, IIT Gandhinagar

Publication: ABC, IOT IEEE Transactions (Impact Factor: 9.3, Status: Published)

Student President, Technology and Research, IIT Gandhinagar

Publication: ABC, IOT IEEE Transactions (Impact Factor: 9.3, Status: Published)